SAGAR JAGTAP

ERP & MIS

9130567152

☑ jagtaps100@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Manager - ERP, MIS & Strategy

Jhamtani

10/2023 - Present

- In depth analysis of Sales, Channel Sales, Digital and Pre-sales leads, CRM estimated collection vs actual collection, Marketing Expense etc using Excel, Google Sheet, Powerbi.
- Analyzing the CPL/ CPV for all the sources, expense data and budget vs actual.
- Optimizing the MIS & ERP systems for all the departments and business units.
- Conducting market surveys using **CRE Matrix** to analyze current **project rates and trends.**
- Successfully implemented Farvision ERP and Maksoftbox Mdoc within required time frame.
- Collaborate with vendors to manage ERP upgrades, ensure timely resolution of system issues, negotiate service contracts and cross departmental queries handling and training.

Junior Engineer - PropTech

Vilas Javdekar Developer

04/2022 - 10/2023

- Designed and developed MIS frameworks to collect, process, and present business-critical data for decision-making.
- Analyzing HR, Sales, Marketing, and CRM data to ensure team productivity using PowerBI.
- Developed and maintain customized reports and dashboards to provide real-time data insights to key stakeholders.
- Train end-users on ERP and MIS functionalities to enhance system adoption and minimize downtime.
- Succesfully implemented Darwinbox and Sales App.

Junior Engineer

Vastu Const

06/2020 - 11/2021

- Develop and maintain automated reporting systems to track billing performance, revenue trends, and key financial metrics
- Manage purchase orders, track inventory levels, and ensure optimal stock availability.

SUMMARY

A strategic and meticulous ERP, MIS & Strategy professional with over 5 years of experience in the deployment, administration, and optimization of ERP and management information systems. Skilled in bridging IT solutions with organizational goals to drive efficiency and growth.

SKILLS



EDUCATION

Civil Engineering, Dr. D. Y. Patil College of Engineering, Akurdi, Pune

LINKS

https://sagar22495.github.io/MyProfile/Info.html https://github.com/Sagar22495

COURSES

Data Analytics With Power BI and SQL, Fialytics

Python for Data Analysis, IT View